Nao.
うえはら よしかわ (上原)吉川
I... want to live alone.
俺一人暮らしがしたいんだ
What?
なお (菜緒)え...
The real reason I moved out of my house
そもそも 俺が家を出たのは
was because of Yuri, but also...
百合のこともあったけど
because I wanted to live on my own.
1人で生きて行けるように なりたかったんだ
I've really wanted to ever since my brother got married.
兄貴が結婚してから すげえそう思ってさ
I knew it was time to stop relying on my brother for everything.
もう兄貴には 頼っちゃいけないんだって こつ
So, I think this is a good chance to...
だからこの機会に
Nao!
よ…吉川
Why are you crying like that?
お前そんなすごい顔で 泣かなくても
Don't you like me anymore, Uehara?
上原君私のこと 嫌いになっちゃつたの?
What?
は?
Were you even listening to me?
お前俺の話 聞いてたか?
Yes, I was, but...
聞いてたよ 聞いてたけど
Don't you want to be with the person you love?
だけど好きな人と 一緒にいたいって思うはずじゃん
Listen to me, would you?
いいかよーく聞け
If we let things stay this way, we'll be living together forever.
このままだとずーっと 一緒に住むことになっちまうだろ
That can be kind of dull.
何かそんなの つまんねえじゃん
It's not dull!
つまんなくないよ!
I don't want to.
俺はイヤなの
Anyway, I've made up my mind.
とにかく決めたから
-I'm against it. -Nao!
私はイヤ 仩原)吉川
Fine. I'm going to work.
じゃあ俺バイト行くから
You cool off and clear your head.
お前も頭冷やして
Think it over when you're calmer.
冷静に考えてみて
Nao!
(まりな)菜緒
Marina!
まりな~
Whoa! What's the matter?
(まりな)おーえっ何? どうした?
Uehara dumped me.
上原君にフラれた
-What?
(光石·まりな)えー!?
So, no more living together.
(まりな)同居解消か
But he didn't say he wanted to break up, right?
でも別れようって 言われたわけじゃないんでしょ?
Yeah,
(菜緒)そうだけど
but it's like the only reason we're a couple is
でもさ 私たちが近くにいるから
that we're living together.
付き合い始めた みたいなもんでしょ
Even now I feel insecure about us.
今でも不安になるんだよね
What if someone else was living with him?
上原君が同居する相手 私じゃなかったら
He'd probably end up liking them instead of me.
その人好きになってたんじゃ ないかなって よつ
Uh-oh, her downward spiral has begun.
(光石)始まったよ ロまつた 負のスパイラル
Don't you worry.
大丈夫 大
I know that Uehara loves you, Nao.
上原君はちゃんと 菜緒のこと好きだから
-He does? -That's right.
好き. (まりな)そうだよ
But I don't think he's ever actually told me that.
ちゃんと好きって 言われたことないかも
Jeez! No matter what you say, it won't help.
(光石)もう何言っても ダメだこりゃ
Calm down, would you?
ああもう落ち着いて!
Why don't you tell me again exactly what he said to you, OK?
あの上原君に どんなふうに言われたのか
"If we let things stay this way, we'll be living together forever.
“このままずーっと一緒に 住むってことになっちまうだろ”
That can be kind of dull."
“そんなの何か つ…つまんねえじゃん”って
Don't cry.
(光石)泣かないで
You know, that sounds more like he's asking you to marry him.
えっそれって 何かプロポーズみたいじゃない?
-Huh? -What do you mean by that?
(菜緒)えっ (光石)ん?どういうこと?
It sounds like he's saying
えつだつて この先上原君は つの えこ
that he's going to be with Nao forever, right?
ずーっと菜緒と 一緒にいるってことでしょ?
Yeah.
(HEE)
The future that Uehara pictures for himself includes Nao!
上原君が描く未来予想図には 菜緒がいるってことじゃん
So, what does that mean?
はいそれってつまり
-Oh! Marriage? -That's right!
あっ結婚? (まりな)そう!
What? You really think so?
えつそ…そうなの!?
-Marry me. -OK.
結婚してください (菜緒)はい
Marry me.
(上原)結婚してくださし.
I'm so happy for you!
もういいないいな
Oh, cut it out, Marina.
ちょっと まりなやめてよ
Wow! I never thought Uehara would propose to Nao!
(光石) ああまさかあの上原が
"Marry me!"
(まりな)結婚してくださしリ
Stop teasing me.
お~い
-Let me have a chance! -No way!
まりな)やっぱ返してください (菜緒)イヤだ
So he was getting ready for marriage by living together. What a stud.
(康太郎)同棲って結婚前提かよ やるなあ
-You're crazy to be jealous about that? -It's kind of arousing.
(弥生) うらやましすぎ (悠人)ちょっと何かいやらしい
-You've got a filthy mind. -No, I don't!
(弥生)何考えてんのよバカ C悠 人)いやいや
Did you hear that Uehara asked Nao
(七瀬)ねえ聞いた? 上原君が吉川さんに
-to marry him? -Seriously?
…たつ だって! こつ (絵梨菜)マジ!?
-What a shock! -I'm so jealous!
(敦子)ちょっとショック (七瀬)でもうらやましい
-I wonder what her answer was. -Me too.
(桜)吉川さん何て言ったのかな? (弥生)気になる
It's all just a rumor.
(エリカ) ってかただの噂でしょ?
I'll never believe it.
私絶対信じない
But everyone's saying it,
(桜)でもみんな言ってるよ
that Uehara proposed to her.
上原君がプロポーズしたって
What?
いっせい (一星)はあ!?
I thought the blackmail thing was solved.
脅迫状は 解決したんじゃねえのかよ?
-We thought it was, but... -But what?
(阿部)そのはずだったんすけど. (一星)けど何だよ
The notes at school were done by someone else.
何か学校での嫌がらせは 別だったみたいで こつにみに
I can't believe this.
何だよそれ
Is that you, Issei?
あれ一星さん?
Oh, I, uh...
えついゃ えついや…
Is something wrong?
(阿部)どうしたんです?
I, uh, just happened to be passing by.
あのたまたま 近く通りかかってな近く
You must be checking up on Nao.
ああもしかして吉川?
What? No, of course not! Are you nuts?
はあ!?お前ちげーよ 何言って…
Hey, let's go back together. I was thinking of dropping by for ramen.
じゃ一緒帰りましょうよ 番星行こうと思ってたんで
OK.
(一星)おお
Today I've really got to lift my spirits with your ramen.
もう今日は食わないと やってらんないっすよ
What happened? Were you turned down again?
何だお前 またフラれたのか?
Actually, this is even worse than that.
いやある意味 それよりショックなことが
Really?
あ?
I heard that Uehara asked Nao to marry him.
何か上原が吉川に プロポーズしたみたいなんですよ
Marry him?
プロポーズ?
It's really tough to handle when it's a girl you like.
何か好きだった子がそういうのって 結構ショックデカくて
Are you coming, Issei?
あれ?一星さん?
Sorry, but you go on ahead.
悪いちょっと先行ってて
-Why? -Sorry.
(一星)悪いな え
The food is great.
ワオいいね
I hope he's home soon.
早く来ないかな
Welcome home.
おかえりなさい
Thanks.
ただいま
Today I pulled out all the stops for us.
今日はいつもより 頑張って作っちゃったんだ~ つにんに
I can see.
仩原) うん
She's as high as a kite.
浮かれまくってんな
-What is it? -Nothing.
何? 何上原)ん? 仩原)ん?
Here you go. There.
どうぞ~はい
-Let's eat. -Let's eat!
いただきます (菜緒)いただきます
How is it?
どう?
I haven't eaten anything yet.
(上原)ん?まだ食ってないよ
-Good. -Do you like it?
仩原) うん (菜緒)おいしい?
It's delicious.
うまい
I'm so glad!
あーよかった
Bon appétit.
いただきます
By the way, about moving--
ところでさあの 引っ越しのことなんだけど
Oh! I'll talk to the landlady about it.
あっ私 大家さんに相談してみるね
I've got to have a positive outlook.
前向きに考えないとね
Yeah.
仩原) うん
-Oh, Uehara. -Hi.
あれ上原君? (上原)おお
-Aren't you going in? -No, I'm OK.
入んないの? (上原)あついや俺は別に
Come on! Let's eat together!
いいからいいから 一緒に食べよ
Oh, they're still closed, but it'll be OK.
あつまだ準備中だけど 大丈夫大丈夫!
Or are you too embarrassed to go in?
あつそれとも ちょっと照れくさい?
Why?
あ?
Don't act dumb. I heard all about it.
もうとぼけちゃつて 聞いたよ~
Yeah, you proposed to Nao, right?
そうそう したんだろプロポーズ
No, I didn't.
してねーよ
Oh, you! Don't be ashamed.
またまたもう照れちゃつて
Like I said, I never proposed to her.
だからした覚えはない
Really?
え?
I've heard all the rumors, but...
何かいろいろ 噂になってるみたいだけど
I didn't.
してない
Have you told Nao?
(まりな)それ菜緒には?
How could I?
言えるわけないだろ
-Let's go! -What? Why?
行こう (上原)は?おい
The sooner you tell her, the better.
こういうのはね 早いほうがいいから
We can't talk about this while she's working.
でもバイト中にするような 話じゃないし
It's fine. They're closed.
(まりな)大丈夫準備中だし
It'll be easier to laugh it off with other people around.
周りに人がいたほうが 笑って流せるから いる
If you told her when you're alone,
2人きりの時に そんなこと言われたら
Nao could die from shock.
菜緒ショックで 死んじゃうかもよ?
She's right.
言えてる
Besides, we might be a little responsible for the rumors.
それに私たちにも ちょっと責任があるっていうか…
-What? -Well, you see...
仩原)え? (まりな)えっいやあの.
At any rate, let's go inside.
まあまあとにかく行こう
Yeah, let's!
行こうはい
Sorry, but we're not open yet.
(菜緒) すいませんまだ準備中で
Uehara!
上原君!
Nao.
菜緒
What are you all doing here?
どうしたの?みんなで
So, you went to a rental agency.
上原君 不動産屋さん行ってきたんだ
Are you guys moving?
(一星)何だお前ら 月刂り 引っ越すのか
-Yeah. -Really?
(菜緒) うん (一星)へえ ヘスー んえ
We had a long talk, and decided to live separately.
(菜緒)いろいろ話し合って 別々に住むことにしたの
What? But why?
(一星)え?何でだよ
-Well... -We've got our reasons.
(菜緒)いや (上原)いろいろあんだよ
-What reasons? -It's none of your business.
(一星)いろいろって何だよ (上原)関係ないだろ
-Didn't you propose? -No, I didn't!
お前プロポーズしたんだろ! (上原) してねーよ!
What?
え?
What's going on here?
どういう意味だよ
Uehara?
上原君?
I'm sorry.
悪いけど 本当に覚えがないんだ
Uh... It's opening time.
(徹平) えっと "営業の時間です
Oh, yeah... that's right!
ああ…おう
-Nao? -Keep a grip on yourself.
(まりな)菜緒 (光石)気を確かに 菜を
OK. I'll be fine.
うん大丈夫大丈夫
Do your best at work, Uehara.
上原君もバイト頑張ってね
I will.
おう
Bye.
じゃあね
Nao!
(一星)吉川!
Hey! Wake up!
おいおい
You OK?
大丈夫かよ?
I'm sorry, Issei.
ごめんいっちゃん
It's OK. Lie back down.
いいから寝とけって
-What about the shop? -It's fine.
あつお店大丈夫? (一星)大丈夫だよ
Dad brought us here by car, then he went back.
車で親父が送ってくれたけど 先帰ったから
I see. Sorry.
そっか ごめんね
I can't believe you passed out.
しかし気絶するかね普通
-Issei? -Yeah?
いっちゃんさ (一星)ん?
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
彼女いたことある?
Well, yeah, sure.
そりゃまあ
Did you ever argue?
ケンカとかした?
Of course.
したよケンカぐらい
Did you ever think
女の子の気持ち
"I can't understand a woman's feelings"?
分かんないなあって よいなのつ 思ったことある?
You bet.
あるある
I see.
そうだよね
I guess it's only natural.
やっぱそっか
Everyone probably thinks the same thing.
みんなそうなのかな
Hey, look,
(一星) まああれだ
if you can't understand what a guy's thinking, then ask me.
男の気持ち分かんない時は 俺に聞け
OK?
なつ?
Once upon a time...
あるところに
Huh?
(一星)ん?
There was a couple that lived together.
一緒に住む カップルがいました
Then suddenly, one day
ある日突然
the guy said he wanted to live separately.
別々に住みたいって言った こいつ 男の人の本音教えてくんない?
Is that what Uehara said?
上原に言われたのか?
What's wrong with him?
何だよそれ
Why did he say it?
教えて
Because he...
相手のことが
stopped liking her.
好きじゃなくなった
I see.
そっか
I thought he was actually asking to marry me.
私プロポーズされたって こつ 勘違いしちゃつた
I'm such an idiot.
バカだよね
How could you possibly think he was asking you to marry him?
どう勘違いしたら プロポーズになんだよ
Issei?
(菜緒)いっちゃん?
I'm sorry.
ごめん
I didn't mean anything by that.
なーんてな
You surprised me.
ああびつくりした
You know...
あのさ
Yes?
(菜緒)ん?
I want you to be mine.
お前もう俺にしとけよ
Are you joking again?
また冗談?
Of course it's a joke. Don't be silly.
なーんて冗談だよバカ!
Oh, cut it out, Issei.
もうやめてよいつちゃん
OK, I'm going now.
(一星)ハァ... じゃあ俺行くわ
-OK. -Bye.
(菜緒) うん (一星) じゃあな
Thanks so much, Issei.
いっちゃんありがとね
No problem.
(一星)おう
I brought her home.
送ってきた
So her job comes with a free ride too?
バイト送迎付きだっけ?
She fainted!
ぶっ倒れたんだよ
What?
え?
I thought I told you not to make her cry.
あいつのこと泣かせんなって 俺言ったよな
I'd never let her cry like she does.
俺だったら こつたら あんな泣かせたりしねえぞ
Take good care of her, dammit.
ちゃんと見ててやれよ
How are you feeling?
体調は?
Good. I'm just fine.
うん 全然大丈夫
Hello? Issei?
もしもしいっちゃん?
-I'm going. -Huh?
先行っとく 仃つ (菜緒)え?
Thanks for yesterday.
昨日はありがとね
Take the day off today. That's an order from your boss.
-星)今日はバイト休めよ これ業務命令
Today, first period is self-study.
(教師1) 1時間目は自習にします
-Yes! -All right!
(生徒たちのはしゃぐ声)
OK, quiet down! Quiet down!
(教師1)はい静かに静かに
-Nao. -Yes?
(教師1)吉川さん (菜緒)はい
Come with me to the counselling room.
ちょっと指導室まで
Really?
え?
We received this.
(教師2) これなんだけどね
And we've heard some rumors that we cannot ignore.
ただのいたずらとは 流せないような噂も耳にしてね
When we hear rumors like this,
(教師3) こういう噂が出た以上は
we have no choice but to confirm their validity.
事実確認をしなければ ならないことになっていてね
Is it true that
(教頭) 君がD組の吉川菜緒さんと
Well...
tha...
Yes, it's true.
事実です
We were the victims of fraud.
私たち詐欺に遭ったんです
We didn't have the money to move...
引っ越しするお金もなくて
So that's the reason you couldn't help living together?
(教師2)それで仕方なく 一緒に住み始めたと
Do your parents know about this?
(教師3)親御さんは ご存じなんですか?
I understand the situation clearly.
(教頭) 事情はよく分かりました
However, as a school,
しかし学校としては
we cannot give tacit approval to an under-age boy and girl living together.
未成年の男女の同居を 黙認するわけにはいきません
I think you understand.
分かりますね?
Yes.
はい
We're going to call your parents now,
(教師1)保護者の方には これから連絡を取って
and ask them to come to the school tomorrow.
明日にでも 学校に来ていただきます
We'll decide what to do after we talk to your parents.
今後のことは親御さんと 話し合って決めますので
Do you understand?
そのつもりで
Yes.
はい
I'm sorry for causing this trouble.
(菜緒)すみませんでした
It's from Uehara.
上原君
It's Mom.
お母さん
Hello?
もしもし
Nao?
(美紀子)菜緒?
Is it still cold there? Do I need to bring a coat?
ねえそっちまだ寒い? 明日羽織るものは必要かな?
I'm sorry about this, Mom.
お母さんごめんね
Don't worry. It will work out somehow.
(美紀子) 大丈夫よ何とかなるわよ
But, Nao...
でもね菜緒
I don't think you'll be able to live there any longer.
もうそこに住み続けるのは 難しいと思う
I know.
(菜緒)分かってる
Evening Star Ramen!
(一星) まいど一番星です
Oh, it's the ramen. This way, please.
(使用人)ああ一番星さん こちらへお願いします
OK, thank you.
(一星)はい失礼します
About the bowls, I'm terribly sorry.
あの丼の件 本当にすいませんでした
It's OK. Your father came and apologized about that the other day.
いえそのことなら先日 お父様が謝罪に来られて
But it was me that broke them.
いや割ったの自分なんです
I really am very, very sorry.
本当に 申し訳ございませんでした
Oh, forget about it.
もういいんですよ
I'll bring you payment.
めつお代持ってきますね
So, Uehara, you've made up your mind?
(ルミ子) 上原君決心したんですね
If we keep living together like this in secret,
仩原) このまま コソコソ一緒に暮らすほうが
it's only going to end up hurting her.
相手を傷つけることにも なりますから
Hello?
(菜緒)もしもし
It's me.
俺だけど
Yes.
うん
Have you had dinner?
(上原)飯食ったか?
Yeah. And you?
うん 上原君は?
The landlady treated me to dinner.
大家さんにごちそうになった
So you're looking for a place?
(菜緒)部屋探してるんだ
Yeah. She said she could get me a place pretty quickly.
うん すぐにでも紹介してくれるって
I see. That's great.
そっか よかった
Yuri got called to the school for tomorrow.
(上原)明日百合が 学校に呼ばれたらしい
Yuri's back in Japan?
ゆりりん帰国してんの?
Yeah. What about your parents?
(上原) うん 親父さんたちは?
They'll be at school tomorrow.
明日学校来るって
I see.
そっか
I wonder what's going to happen to us.
どうなっちやうのかな 私たち
I have no idea either.
俺にもさっぱり分かんねえ
Uehara?
上原君
Yeah?
ん?
Do you... regret... living together?
後悔してる? 同居したこと
What about you?
吉川は?
Not in the least. It surprises me.
びっくりするぐらい してない
That's because you hardly think about it at all.
まあお前は基本 何も考えてないからな
You're so mean!
ひつどい!
I'm thinking about it a lot.
私だっていろいろ考えてるよ
Liar.
(上原) ウソつけ
You're even getting ready to go to bed now.
今だって 早々と寝ようとしてただろ
What? How did...
あついや…
Go ahead. Get to bed. Talk to you later.
(LR) もう寝ろ寝ろ じゃあ切るぞ るそ
Wait! Hold on--
あつちよつ… ちょっと待つ。
I don't regret it either.
俺もしてないよ
Bye.
じゃあな
Let's go, Nao.
まりな)おいしよ 菜緒行こう
OK.
うん
Where is it?
あれ?
-Nao. -Huh?
渼南)吉川さん (菜緒)ん?
Are you looking for your key?
(美南) もしかして鍵を探してるの?
Yes.
そうだけど
Did it have a ribbon key holder?
リボンのキーホルダーのついた?
Give it back!
返して!
That's no way to ask.
(美南)そんな言い方は ないんじゃない?
Where is it?
どこにあるの?
Shiori found it on the floor, so she's taking it to the police.
落とし物は交番に届けようって 詩織が
Uehara, Nao hasn't come back from P.E.
(まりな)上原君 菜緒が戻らないんだよね
Really?
え?
Hey, Mitsuishi. Have you seen Nao?
(まりな)あっねえみっちゃん 菜緒知らない?
She ran out of here just a second ago.
あっさつき すげえダッシュで出てったけど
Is something wrong?
何かあった?
Uehara!
上原君
Are you really going to leave her?
本当にこのまま 離れちやっていいの?
It's none of your business.
関係ないだろ
-Yes, it is our business! -That's right.
(光石)関係なくなんかねーよ! (阿部)そうだよ
We all want you two to be together.
みんなお前らが そうなったらいいなって思ってんだよ
Come on. Try to understand why Nao's insecure.
(まりな)ねえ
She can't tell what your feelings are unless you tell her.
気持ちって言わないと 伝わらないんだよ
Stop!
(菜緒)待って!
Give me back my key.
返してよ!私の鍵
What are you talking about?
詩織)え?何?
It's very important to me. Give it back.
大事な物なの 返して
There's no way you two are living together!
(詩織)同棲とか ありえねえつつーの!
Uh-oh.
(エリカ)あ~あ
I'm terribly sorry for all this trouble.
(教頭)御足労おかけして 申し訳ありません
Please have a seat.
どうぞおかけください
I'd like you to look at these.
これなんですがね
Can you believe her? She's lost her mind.
うわマジ?ヤバっ
That's cold!
Ante...
She is my girlfriend.
仩原) こいつ俺と付き合ってるから
Lean on others when you need to.
頼るところは頼れ
Don't worry. I'm not interested in anyone but you right now.
安心しとけ お前以外に興味ねえから
Uehara, I like you.
(菜緒 )上原君好き
I'll treasure it forever.
く菜緒)一生の宝物にする
"Absence makes the heart grow fonder."
会えない時間が 愛を育ててくれるもんね
There you go crying again.
(上 ) ま~た泣く 原
You mean to tell me that you knew they were living together?
(教頭)では同居はご両親も ご存じだったということですか?
Yes, of course we did.
(和典)はいもちろんです
What the hell are you doing, Nao?
吉川お前 何やってんだよ!
Nao!
EHJII
My key!
鍵が...
If I lose that, then it really will be all over.
あれがないとダメなの 本当に終わっちゃう
Stop this and calm down!
(一星) やめろって落ち着けよ
Let go of me!
(菜緒)放してよ
Nao!
EHJII
I...
俺...
I lied to you.
俺ウソついた
Huh?
え?
The real reason a guy says he wants to live separately
男が別居切り出す 本当の理由は
is that he doesn't want to hurt the girl.
相手のこと 傷つけたくないからだよ
Thank you, Issei.
ありがとういっちゃん
Hello?
もしもし
The situation was really very complex.
(美紀子) いろいろ複雑な事情がありまして
We worried over it quite a bit ourselves.
私たちも悩みましたし
And we talked it over good and long with our daughter.
娘ともよく話し合いましたし
But I still don't think living together was a solution.
しかしそれにしても 同居というのは
They're only 17. And they're a boy and a girl.
17のしかも男女ですよ?
Uhm...
佰刽あの
-It's not just the two of them alone. -Really?
2人きりじゃないですよ? (教頭)え?
I'm living with them too.
私も一緒に住んでますけど
I don't understand.
(教頭) と言いますと?
Uehara's older brother is my husband. He's working overseas now.
ひさし 久志の兄つまり 私の主人が海外勤務で
So I'm living with Uehara and Nao here in Japan.
私が久志と菜緒ちゃんと一緒に 日本で暮らしているんです
It's more like Nao is boarding with us.
菜緒ちゃんはいわゆる 下宿みたいな感じで
So it's not just those two alone?
(教頭) 2人で暮らしているわけでは
No, of course not! They're only high-school kids.
やだまさか 高校生ですよ?
Then what about these?
じゃあこれは?
Oh, there's a lot of that.
あー多いんですよね
Uehara's fans always make a mountain out of a molehill.
久志のファンが あることないこと言って
-He really is handsome, isn't he? -You think so?
上原君かっこいいもんねえ (和典)そうか?
Oh, please.
まさか先生方
No, we weren't taken in.
あついや そういうわけでは…
No, of course you weren't.
まさかですよね?
However, due to these rumors,
(教頭)いやしかし こういう噂が立った以上は
-We don't want other students to see. -I see.
他の生徒たちの目もありますし (美紀子)ええ
We've already decided on moving her out.
引っ越しは もう決めてあります
-Oh my god. She's still at it. -What an idiot.
渼南)ゲッまだやってるし (エリカ)バカじゃないの?
This is hilarious.
ウケる
I think I'll just start sending this out.
これ手当たり次第 送っちゃおっかな
I heard Nao's parents were called in by the vice principal.
吉川の親 教頭に呼ばれてるらしいよ
-Seriously? -Because of this.
(エリカ)マジ? (美南) これのせいで
Oh, yeah! That!
(エリカ)あー出た
That really sent the teachers into a panic.
先生たちも すっかり慌てちやってさ
What are you doing?
渼南)ちょっと
Hey!
え?
I couldn't care less anymore.
何かどうでもよくなってきた
I couldn't care less about Uehara or her anymore.
上原君もあいつも
Let's go.
行こ
I guess she thinks she doesn't have a chance with him.
勝てる気がしないってことか
Hey, wait up.
あっ待ってよ
Hey! Nao!
おい吉川! の
-What are you doing? -Uehara.
何やってんだよ! (菜緒)上原君
I lost my key, Uehara.
上原君 私鍵なくしちゃつて
Wait! My key.
待って鍵...
Nao... let's go home.
吉川うちに帰ろう
-But-- -Don't worry about it.
でも (上原)大丈夫だから
Thank you.
ありがとう
-Nao? -Yes?
(上原)なあ吉川 (菜緒)ん?
Could you tell me why you thought I was asking you to marry me?
どうやったらあれが プロポーズになんのか教えてくれ
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
No matter how much I think about it, I can't figure it out.
俺には いくら考えても分からない
Yeah, you're right.
そうだよね
Now that I think about it, I don't know what I was thinking.
冷静に考えたら そんなわけないもんね
I let myself get all carried away.
何か私 1人で盛り上がっちゃつて…
Were you really that happy about it?
そんなに うれしかったのかねえ
Of course I was happy.
(菜緒) うれしかったんだよ
However...
でも...
even though that wasn't my meaning then...
その時はそういうつもりで 言ったんじゃないけど
I...
俺は…
I do want to be with you forever.
吉川とずつと一緒に いたいと思ってるよ
I don't know what the future holds, but that's how I feel right now.
先のことは分かんねーけど 今はそう思ってるから
Even if it's not here, and even if we live separately,
この部屋じゃなくても 別々に住んでも
let's be together forever.
ずっと
OK.
よし
So you're going to move.
(ルミ子) いよいよ引っ越しですか
I'll miss you.
寂しくなりますねえ
Uhm...
あのもう1つだけ お願いがあるんです
Come in.
(菜緒)はーい
-Long time no see! -Daichi! Nice to see you!
(大地)久しぶり (菜緒)大ちゃん久しぶり
Come in.
どうぞどうぞ
-Is everyone here? -Yeah.
(大地)もうみんないる? (菜緒) うん
Oh, long time no see.
85久しぶり
-Daichi! -Hi!
まりな)大地先輩! (大地)よう!
That university smell makes you even more handsome.
何か大学生の香り ますますかっこいい!
-Really? -Yes.
(大地)そうか? (まりな) うん な) つ
Hi.
どうも
-It's been a while. -Who's that? Introduce me.
(大地)久しぶり (ななこ)誰誰?紹介してよ
You're just a kid still.
(まりな)お子ちゃまには まだ早いから!
What are you talking about? Come on, introduce me.
(ななこ)何で?いいでしよ いいじゃん…
Here you go. It's ready.
(明)はいはいできたよ
It's shrimp.
IE IE
Look at you! You're as handsome as ever, Daichi!
(美紀子)あっ大ちゃん 相変わらずイケメンねえ
He's handsome too. Who's that? Introduce me.
かっこいい ねえ誰誰?紹介してよ
How come she's not asking who I am?
ねえその"誰?"っていうの 何で俺にないの?
She's ignoring me too.
俺も 俺もスルーされたから
Thank you.
ありがとう
Thank you!
(菜緒)ありがとう
Do you want some pot stickers?
ねえ餃子食べる?
Thank you. Here's the soy sauce.
あつありがとう はいしょうゆ
Thanks. Pour some on.
あっありがとう かけていいよ
It's time to propose a toast to Uehara and Nao's future together.
(百合)えーそれでは 久志と菜緒ちゃんの前途を祝して
Wait! Is that alcohol?
ちょっと待て百合 それ酒じゃねえの?
Don't be such a wet blanket.
(百合)固いこと言わないの
OK. Cheers!
じゃあ乾杯!
-Cheers!
(一同)乾杯!
My lease here starts from today.
(菜緒) 私今日からここに住むし
What are you talking about? Look, Room 305!
(上原)何言ってんだよ 確かに305号室
Me too, Room 305!
(菜緒)私も305号室!
-Huh?
上原·菜緒)えっ!? えつ
Are you packed?
準備は?
Yep.
うん (チャイム)
Polar Bear Moving!
(業者) しろくま引っ越しセンターです
-Coming.
上原,菜緒)はーい
OK, I'll see you.
じゃあ行くね
Yeah.
おう
The truck is that way.
私車あっちだから
Mine's that way.
俺あっち
OK.
うん
Bye.
じゃあ
Uehara!
(菜緒)上原君!
Sorry. It's nothing.
何でもない
See you.
じゃあね
Nao!
吉川
I love you.
好きだよ
I know.
知ってる
Room 305 is vacant now.
305号室ね空きましたよ
But there's a condition regarding the length of the lease.
ただ期間に 条件がありましてね
Here goes!
よし!
Thank you. Good bye.
(業者)では失礼します
Ah!
(菜緒) うわっ
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい!
Uehara.
(菜緒)上原君
Why are you here?
何で?
Why am I here?
仩原)何でって
Because this is where I live now.
ここは今日から 俺が住むんだよ
I'm in 402.
402号室
Really?
え?
Where are you?
吉川は?
I'm... in 401.
私401号室
Oh... do you think...
あ...もしかして
-the landlady did this?
(上原·菜緒)大家さん!?
I have another favor to ask.
(上原)もう1つだけ お願いがあるんです
Three years from now when we're adults,
3年後成人したら
I'd like to move back into that place...
もう一度 あの部屋に戻りたいんです
with her.
あいつと一緒に
We're neighbors.
お隣さんだね
What was the point in moving?
引っ越した意味あんのかな